TYRONE W. NOLASCO

https://github.com/sh1ggy | https://sh1ggy.tk

E: tyronewessnolasco@gmail.com

P: (+61) 401 687 774

OBJECTIVE

Currently based in Brisbane, working a Systems Support Specialist at Sonic IT with a proficiency in verbose incident documentation and communications under the pressure of customer and stakeholder expectations. I have a desire to further my communication skills as well as expand upon my background in web development by taking advantage of opportunities to work outside of my comfort zone.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sonic IT

May. 2022 - Current

System Support Specialist

Brisbane, Queen Street

- Responsible for troubleshooting medical software supported by Sonic IT to resolve tickets raised by medical sites across Australia, achieving an average of 6+ ticket resolutions per day.
- Maintenance of case-by-case incident documentation and team-wide knowledge articles as a part of a collaborative effort to document the support process for various softwares.
- Management of critical incidents that require both quick communication as well as adaptability
- Responsible for engaging with internal Sonic IT teams & external vendors via thorough communication to assist with incident resolution and management of critical incidents.

Wings Education

Aug. 2021 – May. 2022

IT Support Lead & Social Media Lead

Brisbane, Fortitude Valley

- Responsible for management and development of a PHP-based LMS website using Moodle & SQL
- IT hardware and software support to maintain Gold Coast and Fortitude Valley computer labs
- Lead social media designer, video editor and co-ordinator for company marketability.
- IT intern training for basic IT troubleshooting, social media designs and LMS maintenance.
- High level communication within a small business environment & maintenance of internal company documentation

EDUCATION & TRAINING

2021 - 2023

RM Display and Information Guidance System (DIGS) Project React & NodeJS Continuation of the QUT Capstone Project outside of the scope of university work. https://github.com/ProPablo/rm_dashboard

- Development of the project's final client, backend and application features in a team of two in order to push the project to be ready for production with real-world users at Redland Museum.
- Acting project manager responsible for defining and allocating tasks that aligned with project scope as well as managing project expectations with the Project Owner via regular online meetings, email correspondence and onsite visits.

2018 - 2021

Queensland University of Technology

Bachelor Information Technology (Computer Science)

Minors: Engineering Foundations & Mobile App Development

2013 - 2017

Corinda State High School | Certificate II in Active Volunteering

OCE - OP 6

PROJECTS & AWARDS

2022 - Present **Personal Website & Blog**

NextJS, TypeScript Personal website to experiment with web development and create a place to write my

programming-focussed blog

https://sh1ggy.tk

2021 UQCS Hackathon

NextJS, TypeScript Bingo Butler

Discord bot that generates links for a speed-run bingo mini-game depending on the text

channel you invoke it in. Used a MERN stack and handled the manipulation of data and

conditionally rendering it to the front-end https://github.com/sh1ggy/bingobutler

2021 GMTK: Joined Together

Godot, GDScript Parity

Learned basics of game development and made a 'bullet-hell inventory management' game

in 48 hours using Godot https://sh-ggy.itch.io/parity

2019 Brisbane Mobile App Hackathon, 2nd Place

Android Studio Responsible for creating a labour search and job shift management app

https://github.com/sh1ggy/hackathon19-TDRJKM-android

SKILLS

• Programming Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, C#, C, SQL, Java, Python

• **Technologies & Frameworks:** NextJS, React, React Native, NodeJS, Godot, Markdown, LaTeX

PERSONAL INTERESTS

Social Activities: University of Queensland Computing Society, CODE Network

• Interests: Hackathons, game jams, note-taking/documentation and rhythm games

REFERENCES

Russell Dinte: Anhad Ahuja:

Project Manager & IT at Redland Museum

E: russdinte@bigpond.com
P: +61 7 3286 3494

Programming Teammate
E: anhadrs@gmail.com
P: +61 490 779 437